Guide to the Stanford Channel Master Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videos (Box 1)
  - Women and Health
    - Women's Health, Women's Lives: Health Care Reform for the New Century, 98-1732 (Box 125)
    - Ceremony Medicine: Ancient Wisdom for Modern Times, 00-1739 (Box 126)
    - Eating Disorders: Patient and Physician Perspectives, 00-1740 (Box 126)
    - Women and Heart Disease: The Silent Epidemic, 00-1741 (Box 126)
    - Health Concerns of Lesbians, Bisexuals, Transgendered and Intersexual People", 00-1742 (Box 126)
    - The Social and Environmental Context of Asian Women's Health, 00-1743 (Box 126)
    - The Alma Mater of Healing, 99-1738 (Box 126)
    - Gynecologic Cancers: What's New and What We Need, 99-1733 (Box 126)
    - Mirror, Mirror: Women and Body Image, 99-1734 (Box 126)
    - Women's Health: How Do We Stack Up?, 99-1735 (Box 126)
    - Strategies to Reduce Health Disparities of Older African American Women, 99-1736 (Box 126)
    - Organizing Asian and Pacific Islander Girls: An Intervention for Reproductive Health, 99-1737 (Box 126)
    - Invisible Toxicity: Pesticide Threats to Women's Health, 00-1744 (Box 127)
    - Women Without Children: Reconceiving Adulthood, 00-1745 (Box 127)
    - Discovering Our Gifts -- the Myers Briggs Test, 01-1746 (Box 127)
  - Stanford Science
    - The NASA Mars Exploration Program, 97-2001 (Box 127)
    - The New Revelations of the Moons of Jupiter from Galileo, 97-2003 (Box 127)
    - Earthquakes, Armageddon and the Dead Sea Scrolls, 97-2004 (Box 127)
    - Science in Fiction, 97-2005 (Box 127)
    - Sorting Out the Climate Confusion in the Wake of Kyoto, 98-2006 (Box 127)
    - Mapping Our Destinies: Human Genome Project, 98-2007 (Box 127)
    - Laser Tweezers: A New Way to Grasp Matter, 98-2008 (Box 127)
    - The Discovery of Extra-Solar Planets and What's Next?, 97-2002 (Box 127)
    - A Symposium Honoring Felix Bloch, 98-2009/a (Box 128)
    - A Symposium Honoring Felix Bloch, 98-2009/b (Box 128)
    - A Symposium Honoring Felix Bloch tape #1, 98-2009/c (Box 128)
    - A Symposium Honoring Felix Bloch tape #2, 98-2009/c (Box 128)
    - Gene Therapy: Prospects for the Next Decade, 99-2011/c (Box 128)
    - Gene Therapy: Prospects for the Next Decade, 99-2011/d (Box 128)
    - Gene Therapy: Prospects for the Next Decade tape #1, 99-2011/e (Box 128)
    - Gene Therapy: Prospects for the Next Decade tape #2, 99-2011/e (Box 128)
    - Aspirin: Heart Attacks and Ulcers, 99-2012 (Box 128)
    - How Can We Communicate Effectively: Squeezing Bits Efficiently, 99-2013 (Box 128)
    - Hydrogen as an Energy Source, 44197 (Box 129)
    - What Eco-Systems Do for Society, 99-2014 (Box 129)
    - PGES Works-in-Progress Symposium: Genetic Testing tape #1, 99-2015 (Box 129)
    - PGES Works-in-Progress Symposium: Genetic Testing tape #2, 99-2015 (Box 129)
    - The Digital Michelangelo Project AND Laser-Aided Manufacturing, 99-2016 (Box 129)
    - Humans/Machines: The Robotics Laboratory, 99-2017 (Box 129)
    - To Infinity and Beyond: Gravity Probe 'B' Lab, 99-2018 (Box 129)
    - Cool Stuff: What IS Materials Science?, 99-2019 (Box 129)
    - What Happens at Absolute Zero, 99-2020 (Box 129)
    - The Final Frontiers: From the Poles to Mars tape #1, 99-2010 (Box 128/B)
    - The Final Frontiers: From the Poles to Mars tape #2, 99-2010 (Box 128/B)
    - Gene Therapy: Prospects for the Next Decade tape #1, 99-2011/a (Box 128/B)
    - Gene Therapy: Prospects for the Next Decade tape #2, 99-2011/a (Box 128/B)
    - Gene Therapy: Prospects for the Next Decade tape #1, 99-2011/b (Box 128/B)
    - Gene Therapy: Prospects for the Next Decade tape #2, 99-2011/b (Box 128/B)
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference on Human Rights, Conflict and Reconciliation
    - Children's Rights: The Need to Establish Safe Havens for Children of War, 98-2202 (Box 130)
    - Democracy & Diplomacy in the Asia-Pacific Region, 98-2201 (Box 130)
    - Role of Indigenous People in a Democratic Guatemala, 98-2203 (Box 131)
    - Reconciliation in Post-Apartheid South Africa: Experiences of the Truth Commission, 98-2204 (Box 131)
    - International Code of Conduct for Arms Transfers, 98-2205 (Box 131)
    - U.N. Declaration of Rights & Its Impact on Asian Values and Democratic Principles, 98-2206 (Box 131)
    - The Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation and the International Campaign to Ban Landmines, 98-2207 (Box 131)
    - International Organization in the Campaign to Ban Landmines, 98-2208 (Box 131)
    - The Need for Compassion in Society: The Case of Tibet, 98-2209 (Box 131)
    - Closing Remarks and Press Conference, 98-2210 (Box 131)
  - Cover to Cover: The Stanford Channel Book Club
    - Life Writing, 99-2302 (Box 131)
    - Literary Prizes, 99-2301 (Box 131)